<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Just4Today</string><string name="et_hint">Enter message here</string>
    <string name="option_one">The 12 Steps</string>
    <string name="option_two">NA Meeting</string>
    <string name="button_one">Call Landline</string>
    <string name="button_two">Show Map</string><string name="meeting" >\"For where two or three gather together
    because they are mine, I am there among them.\" - Matthew 18:20
        
    \n\nCome and join our meeting:
    
    \n\nHealing Path Foundation-HP, Inc.
    \n#25 Newport st., cor. Marlboro st., East Fairview, Quezon City, Philippines
    \nTel. number:  +632 9395917
        
    \n\nEvery Sunday 8:45 - 9:45 am
    </string><string-array name="twelve_steps">
                <item>1. We admitted that we were powerless over our addiction, that
our lives had become unmanageable.</item>
                <item>2. We came to believe that a Power greater than ourselves
could restore us to sanity.</item>
                <item>3. We made a decision to turn our will and our lives over to the
care of God as we understood Him.</item>
                <item>4. We made a searching and fearless moral inventory of
ourselves.</item>
                <item>5. We admitted to God, to ourselves, and to another human
being the exact nature of our wrongs.</item>
                <item>6. We were entirely ready to have God remove all these defects
of character.</item>
                <item>7. We humbly asked Him to remove our shortcomings.</item>
                <item>8. We made a list of all persons we had harmed and became
willing to make amends to them all.</item>
                <item>9. We made direct amends to such people wherever possible,
except when to do so would injure them or others.</item>
                <item>10. We continued to take personal inventory and when we were
wrong promptly admitted it.</item>
                <item>11. We sought through prayer and meditation to improve our
conscious contact with God as we understood Him, praying
only for knowledge of His will for us and the power to carry
that out.</item>
                <item>12. Having had a spiritual awakening as a result of these steps,
we tried to carry this message to addicts, and to practice
these principles in all our affairs.</item>
        </string-array>
    <color name="headfirst">#ff8d8d8d</color>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">593917504072789</string>
    
    
    
    
    
</resources>
